MY RESUME

FATIN ADILAH BT ABD WAHAB Lot 3186K, Batu 15, Kg Paya Jaras Dalam, 47000 Sungai Buloh, Selangor 019-6057355 aten.adila@yahoo.com.my



OBJECTIVE

To learn new knowledge, new experience for enhance my skills and abilities based on the position given. New environment can make me able to use my soft skills, and other expertise to work well with others in organization for achieving the goal and objectives.

PERSONAL PARTICULAR

Date of Birth: 23 February 1994

. 20 1 00 1 daily 100 1

Gender: Female

Marital Status: Single

Nationality: Malaysian

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND AND QUALIFICATIONS



March 2014 - Jan 2017

Universiti Teknologi MARA, Cawangan Kelantan, Kampus Machang

Bachelor of Office System Management with Honors

Final CGPA: 3.23

April 2012 – April 2013

Kolej Matrikulasi Perlis, Arau, Perlis Indera Kayangan

Final CGPA: 2.83

2010 - 2011

SMK Bandar Baru Sungai Buloh, Selangor

SPM (2A, 3A-, 2B+, 1C+, 1E)

WORK EXPERIENCES



Nov 2011 - March 2012

- OYL Manufacturing Company Sdn Bhd
- Production Operator at Wiring Department



Oct 2013 - Feb 2014

- ➢ BINATEX Sdn Bhd
- Account Clerk

Sept 2016 - Dec 2016

- > Malaysian Sheet Glass Sdn Bhd
- Internship (4 months)
- Human Resource Assistant



EXTRA - CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES



2014

- Secretary in AWESOME Club at UiTM Kelantan, Kampus Machang
- Members of Office Management System Association (OMSA)
- Participate SIIDCOM 2014 (Student Innovation Invention and Design Competition)
- Participate in "Program Jelajah Informasi Mesra Jabatan Kehakiman Syariah Malaysia (JKSM)
- Facilitator in MINDA (Masyarakat & IPT Nadi Destini Anak Bangsa) Program

2015

- Participate in Program 1 Citizen
- > Team Building AWESOME
- ➤ The organizer for UKHUWAH BOOSTER (Facilitator)
- > Participate in Volunteer Malaysia
- > Participate in Walks Towards Professional Career Programme at Bank Negara Malaysia

2016

Volunteer Ekspo Selangkah ke UiTM 2016 Program

COMPUTER SKILLS



- Proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access
- Ability to use typing skills
- Proficient in SPSS Software

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS



- ➤ Able to cope with new environment
- Motivated person
- Can increase self-esteem
- ➤ Ability to work independent or in a group
- > Able to work hard
- Intermediary language: Malay (Excellent), English (Moderate)

REFERENCES



The following persons have agreed to provide any additional information regarding my qualifications and others.

1. Name: Puan Nik Sarina Binti Nik Md Salleh

Position: Research Supervisor Faculty of Business and Management **Institution:** Universiti Technologi MARA (UiTM) Machang, Kelantan

Mobile: 012-9641480

2. Name: Puan Nurhidayati Binti Tasnir

Position: Senior Executive Human Resources **Company:** Malaysian Sheet Glass Sdn Bhd

Mobile: 012-7264285